Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory3 Mss.B.B61.inventory03
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents C
  - Cummings, T.F. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 1p
  - Cummins, Dr. Harold (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 29; 1p
    - From Reichert, E., 1935 Sep. 9
    - To Reichert, E., 1935 Sep. 6; 1p
  - Cun, J. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 24; 2p
  - Cunard White Star, Ltd. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 1; 1p
  - Cunliffe, J.W. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15
  - Cureton, T.K., Jr. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 26; 1p
  - Curme, George O. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 1p
  - Current Literature Publishing Co. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 13
  - Curry, W.A. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p
  - Curtis (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 6
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 6
  - Curtis, B. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 1; 1p
  - Curtis, C. Carlton [and C.] (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 27; 2p
      - co-signers: Frank, Waldo
      - Dos Passos, John
      - Steffens, Lincoln
    - From Corner, George, 1908 Nov. 28
  - Curtis, Natalie (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 June 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 11917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 15; 8p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1909 May 11
    - To Boas, 1909 June 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 20
  - Curtis, Roy (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 20; 1p
  - Curtiss, D.K. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
  - Cushing, Frank Hamilton (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1894 June 23
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 5; 3p
  - Cushing, H. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 27; 1p
  - Cuthbert, Margaret (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 26; 1p
  - Cutting, B.M. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 9; 5p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 30
  - Cutting, Starr Willard (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 3p
  - Cuyer, E. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 19
  - Cuyler, H.F. (Box 19)
    - see Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
  - Czaplicka, M.A. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 May 15
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 2p
  - Czekanowski Jan (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1913 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 June 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 27; 2p
  - Czellitzer & Neustaetter (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 15